<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.svgpart</id>
  <!--
    Appstream model currently does not support the idea of generic addons
    See https://github.com/ximion/appstream/issues/157
    As intermediate work-around some typical consumers are listed explicitely.
  -->
  <extends>org.kde.ark.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.kate.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.kdevelop.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>SVG Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">جزء ك عارض صور اس في جي</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Визуализатор на SVG за KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KPart del visualitzador de SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">La KPart del visor de SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KPart pro prohlížení souborů SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">SVG-Betrachter-KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">SVG Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">SVG Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">SVG-Rigardila KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KPart del visor SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">SVG erakusle KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">SVG-katselin-KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Afficheur « SVG » KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KPart de visor de SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">רכיב KDE להצגת SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">एसवीजी प्रदर्शक केपार्ट</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">SVG-megjelenítő KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KPart Visor de SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">SVG Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="ie">Un KPart de visor SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Visore KPart SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">SVG-ის KPart-ში ნახვა</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">SVG 뷰어 KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">SVG-viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KPart-framvisar for SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KPart przeglądarki SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KPart de Visualização de SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KPart do visualizador de SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KPart для просмотра SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">SVG दर्शक KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KPart SVG prehliadača</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">SVG Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">SVG KPart-visning</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">SVG Görüntüleyicisi KPart'ı</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KPart для перегляду SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">KPart trình xem SVG</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSVG Viewer KPartxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">SVG 查看器 KPart 组件</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">SVG 檢視器 KPart</name>
  <summary>Rendered display of SVG files in KParts-using software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">يستعرض صور اس في جي SVG في التطبيقات التي تستخدم جزء ك</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Визуализатор на файлове SVG за приложения, използващи KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Mostra renderitzats els fitxers SVG en el programari que utilitza les KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mostra renderitzats els fitxers SVG en el programari que utilitza les KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zpracované zobrazení SVG v aplikacích využívajících KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Anzeige von SVG-Dateien in Software, die KParts verwendet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Αποτύπωση SVG αρχείων σε λογισμικό με KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Rendered display of SVG files in KParts-using software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Bildigo de SVG-dosieroj en programoj uzantaj KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Visualización renderizada de archivos SVG para software que usa KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KPart darabilten softwareei SVG fitxategiak errendatuta azaltzea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">SVG-tiedostojen hahmonnettu näyttö KPartsia käyttäviin ohjelmiin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Affichage rendu pour les fichiers « SVG » par un logiciel utilisant KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Visualización renderizada de ficheiros SVG en software que usa KParts.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">תצוגה מעובדת של קובצי SVG בתוכנה שמשתמשת ברכיבים של KDE‏ (KParts)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">सॉफ़्टवेयर का उपयोग करके केपार्ट में एसवीजी फ़ाइलों का रेंडर किया गया प्रदर्शन</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">SVG-fájlok renderelt megjelenítése KPartot használó szoftverekben</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Schermo rendite de files SVG in software usante KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Tampilan ter-render pada file-file SVG dalam perangkat lunak menggunakan KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ie">Monstrar files SVG in programmas quel usa KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione renderizzata dei file SVG nel software che utilizza KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">SVG ფაილების რენდერი KPart-ის გამომყენებელი პროგრამით</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KParts를 사용하는 프로그램에서 SVG 파일을 렌더링하여 표시합니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Toonbare weergave van SVG-bestanden in software die KParts gebruikt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Vising av SVG-filer i program som støttar KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie plików SVG w oprogramowaniu używającym KPartów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Visualização de ficheiros de desenhos SVG nas aplicações que usam o KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição renderizada de arquivos SVG nos aplicativos que usam o KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Показ обработанного содержания файлов SVG в программном обеспечении с поддержкой KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">KParts-उपयोगेन तन्त्रांश मध्ये SVG सञ्चिकानां प्रदर्शनं प्रतिपादितम् कृतम्</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vykreslené zobrazenie súborov SVG v softvéri používajúcom KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Preglednik SVG KPart omogoča prikaz SVG datotek z uporabo KParts.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Återgiven vy för SVG-filer i programvara som använder KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">SVG dosyalarının KParts kullanan yazılımda sunulmuş görüntüsü</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Показ обробленого вмісту файлів SVG у програмному забезпеченні із підтримкою KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Bộ hiển thị kết xuất các tệp SVG trong các phần mềm dùng KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxRendered display of SVG files in KParts-using softwarexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">在使用 KParts 的软件中渲染显示 SVG 文件</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">提供利用 KParts 的軟體顯示渲染後的 SVG 檔案的功能</summary>
  <description>
    <p>The SVG Viewer KPart allows KParts-using software to display SVG files in a rendered view.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكن عارض صور اس في جي التطبيقات التي تستخدم جزء ك من تصيير وعرض ملفات اس في جي.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Визуализатор на SVG за KPart позволява приложения, използващи KParts да показват файлове SVG в режим на преглед.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">La KPart del visualitzador de SVG permet que el programari que utilitza les KParts, mostri els fitxers SVG en una vista renderitzada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">La KPart del visor de SVG permet que el programari que utilitza les KPart, mostre els fitxers SVG en una vista renderitzada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die SVG-Betrachter-Komponente befähigt Software, die KParts verwendet, zur Anzeige von Dateien im SVG-Format.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το πρόγραμμα KPart προβολής SVG επιτρέπει σε λογισμικό με KParts να αποτυπώνει SVG αρχεία.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The SVG Viewer KPart allows KParts-using software to display SVG files in a rendered view.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">La SVG-Rigardila KPart permesas al KParts-uzanta programaro montri SVG-dosierojn en bildita vido.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El KPart del visor SVG permite al software que usa KParts mostrar archivos SVG en una vista renderizada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">SVG erakusle KPart-ek KPart darabilten softwareei SVG fitxategiak errendatutako ikuspegian azaltzen aukera eskaintzen die.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">SVG-katselin-KPart sallii KPartsia käyttäviä ohjelmien näyttävät SVG-tiedostot hahmonnettuina.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'afficheur « KPart » de fichiers « svg » permet à un logiciel utilisant « KParts » d'afficher les fichiers « SVG » dans un affichage de rendu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O KPart de visor de SVG permite ao software que usa KParts amosar ficheiros SVG nunha vista renderizada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">רכיב ה־KDE‏ (KPart) להצגת SVG מאפשר לתוכנות שמשתמשות ב־KParts להציג קובצי SVG לאחר עיבוד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">एसवीजी व्यूअर केपार्ट,केपार्ट्स-उपयोग करने वाले सॉफ़्टवेयर को एसवीजी फ़ाइलों को रेंडर किए गए दृश्य में प्रदर्शित करने के लिए सहायता करता है। </p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az SVG-megjelenítő KPart lehetővé teszi az azt használó alkalmazásoknak SVG-fájlok megjelenítését egy renderelt nézetben.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Le visor de SVG KPart permitte a software usante KParts de monstrar files SVG in un vista rendite.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">SVG Viewer KPart memungkinkan perangkat lunak menggunakan KPart untuk menampilkan file-file SVG dalam tampilan yang ter-render.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ie">Li Visor de SVG de KParts permisse programmas quel usa KParts previder files SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il visore KPart SVG consente al software che utilizza KPart di visualizzare i file SVG in una vista renderizzata.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">SVG-ის Kpart-ში ნახვა საშუალებას გაძლევთ პროგრამებში, რომლებიც KParts-ს იყენებენ, დარენდერებული SVG ფაილები აჩვენოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">SVG 뷰어 KPart를 사용하면 KParts를 사용하는 소프트웨어에서 SVG 파일을 렌더링해서 볼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De SVG-viewer van KPart stelt software die KParts gebruikt in staat SVG-bestanden in een toonbare weergave te tonen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KPart-framvisaren for SVG lèt deg visa filer SVG-format i alle program som støttar KPart.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KPart przeglądarki SVG umożliwia oprogramowaniu, używającemu KPartów na wyświetlanie plików SVG jako widoki.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KPart de Visualização de SVG permite às aplicações que usam o KParts apresentarem os ficheiros SVG numa área respectiva.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KPart do visualizador de SVG permite que os aplicativos que usam o KParts mostrem o arquivo SVG renderizado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Модуль просмотра данных SVG позволяет просматривать обработанное содержание файлов SVG в любом программном обеспечении с поддержкой KParts.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">SVG Viewer KPart KParts-उपयोगं कुर्वन्तं तन्त्रांशं SVG सञ्चिकाः प्रतिपादित दृश्ये प्रदर्शयितुं शक्नोति ।.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Prehliadač SVG Viewer KPart umožňuje softvéru používajúcemu KParts zobrazovať súbory SVG  renderovanom zobrazení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Preglednik SVG KPart omogoča programski opremi, ki uporablja KParts, za prikaz upodobitve datotek SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">SVG KPart-visning tillåter program som använder KParts att visa filer med SVG-format i en återgiven vy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">SVG Görüntüleyicisi KPart'ı, KParts kullanan yazılımların SVG dosyalarını işlenmiş bir görünümde sunmasına olanak tanır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Модуль перегляду даних SVG надає змогу переглядати оброблений вміст файлів SVG у будь-якому програмному забезпеченні із підтримкою KParts.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">KPart trình xem SVG cho phép các phần mềm dùng KPart có thể hiển thị tệp SVG trong một khung xem kết xuất.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe SVG Viewer KPart allows KParts-using software to display SVG files in a rendered view.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">SVG 查看器 KPart 组件让使用 KParts 的软件能够在一个视图中显示渲染后的 SVG 文件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">SVG 檢視器這個 KPart 讓利用 KPart 的軟體能夠渲染並顯示 SVG 格式的檔案。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://commits.kde.org/svgpart</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=svgpart</url>
  <update_contact>kossebau_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/svgpart/svgpart.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.1.23084" date="2023-12-07"/>
    <release version="1.1.23083" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="1.1.23082" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="1.1.23081" date="2023-09-14"/>
  </releases>
</component>
